[{"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填", "content": [{"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "一共有", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个球，一共有", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个圆柱体", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [1, 3], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从左边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是球，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是长方体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [2, 5, 8], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填", "content": [{"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "一共有", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个球，一共有", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个圆柱体", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [1, 3], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "content": [{"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从左边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是球，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是长方体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [6, 2, 3], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "content": [{"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从左边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是球，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是长方体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [2, 7, 8], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填", "content": [{"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从左边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是圆柱体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [1, 3, 6], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填", "content": [{"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "一共有", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个球，一共有", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个圆柱体", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [1, 3], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填", "content": [{"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "一共有", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个球，一共有", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个圆柱体", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [1, 3], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从左边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是圆柱体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [3, 4, 7], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从右边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是圆柱体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [2, 3, 5], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填", "content": [{"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从右边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是圆柱体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [5, 7, 8], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填", "content": [{"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从右边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是圆柱体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [1, 4, 6], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "content": [{"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从左边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是球，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是长方体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [2, 3, 5], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填", "content": [{"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从左边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是圆柱体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [5, 6, 8], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填", "content": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "一共有", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个球，一共有", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个圆柱体", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [1, 3], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填", "content": [{"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从右边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是圆柱体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [2, 3, 7], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从左边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是球，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是长方体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [8, 3, 7], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "content": [{"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从左边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是球，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是长方体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [4, 1, 2], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填", "content": [{"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从左边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是圆柱体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [6, 7, 8], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "content": [{"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从左边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是球，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是长方体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [2, 1, 5], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填", "content": [{"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从左边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是圆柱体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [3, 5, 6], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填。", "content": [{"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从左边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是球，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是长方体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [8, 3, 4], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填", "content": [{"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "从右边数，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个，第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个和第", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个是圆柱体。", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [1, 2, 8], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}, {"body": [{"type": "know-cube-color", "showType": "1", "stem": "数一数，填一填", "content": [{"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_3.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "orb", "src": "v2/通用/基本平面图形/圆线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_2.svg"}, {"type": "cylinder", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/圆柱体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cuboid", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/长方体线条_1.svg"}, {"type": "cube", "src": "v2/通用/基本立体图形/正方体线条_1.svg"}], "textList": [{"desc": "一共有", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个球，一共有", "type": "text"}, {"desc": "", "type": "input"}, {"desc": "个圆柱体", "type": "text"}]}], "answers": [1, 3], "knowledges": "认识左右、5以内数的排序、认识长方体、认识正方体、认识球体、认识圆柱体、5以内的数", "resource": "resource", "type": "填空&操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-6-5-05"}]